And with that, we've reached an important milestone.
이제 중요한 이정표에 도달했어요
The first week of our eight week journey is complete, and there's been an awful lot covered.
8주간의 여정 중 첫 주가 끝났습니다 많은 걸 다뤄야 했죠
And congratulations for making it to this point.
여기까지 온 걸 축하해요
At this point, just to recap, you're in a position to describe the history of Transformers and the
간단히 정리해 보죠 트랜스포머의 역사와 충격적인 지난 몇 년을 설명해야
shocking last few years.
하는데요
The use of tokens, tokenization, the importance of context windows and exactly what that means, where
토큰 사용, 토큰화 컨텍스트 윈도우의 중요성 그리고 이것이 정확히 무슨 의미인지
to go to look up API costs, and a lot more like that.
API 비용은 어디서 확인하는지 등 많은 것들이 있죠
You've really got hands on experience looking at a bunch of different frontier models, both the big
빅 식스라는 여러 회사의 모델과 그 안의 모델 그리고 최신
six companies, but also some of the models within them and some of the very latest innovations.
혁신 모델을 직접 살펴본 경험이 많으시잖아요
And we've seen how something like count, how many times letter A appears in the sentence is something
A가 문장에 몇 번 나오는지 세는 건 Lms에겐 놀라울 정도로 어려운 일입니다
surprisingly hard for Llms, even some of the very top ones.
제일 위에 있는 것도 마찬가지죠
And now, with your understanding of tokenization, you probably have a very good sense as to why.
이제 토큰화를 이해하셨으니 그 이유도 잘 아실 텐데요
And then most importantly, you're at this point, hopefully you are confidently able to use the OpenAI
그리고 가장 중요한 건 이 시점에서 OpenAI API를 자신 있게 사용할 수 있길 바라는
API, Including adding in things like streaming and markdown.
겁니다 스트리밍이나 마크다운 같은 걸 추가하는 것도요
You've built your own tool with the assignment, and you've also used the exercise we did.
과제와 함께 여러분만의 도구를 만들고 우리가 한 연습도 사용했죠
You made multiple calls to LMS and you've played around with the system prompts.
LMS에 여러 번 전화했고 시스템 프롬프트도 조작했죠
You've got a good understanding of how you can use the system prompt for things like setting tone,
시스템 프롬프트를 어떻게 사용하는지 잘 알고 있죠 톤 설정이나 응답 문자
character of the response, as well as giving the specific instructions.
같은 거요 구체적인 지시도 할 수 있고요
And you also understand about using both single shot and Multi-shot prompting as a way to get more accurate,
그리고 단발과 다발 프롬핑을 LM에서 보다 정확하고 강력하고 반복 가능한 결과를 얻기 위한 방법으로
robust, repeatable results from the LM.
사용하는 것도 이해하시죠? get it
And to boot, you've also added in using the llama API to call the models running on your box directly.
부팅하기 위해 llama API 사용도 추가했어요 컴퓨터에서 직접 실행되는 모델을 호출하기 위해서요
It's not something that we'll be doing, particularly going forwards.
앞으로 그런 일은 없을 거예요
When we get to using open source models.
오픈 소스 모델을 사용하게 되면요.
We'd rather use hugging face code when we can actually really get into the internals and start examining
Get-Tuck Season 2 닙턱 시즌 2 차라리 포옹하는 얼굴 코드를 사용하죠 내부의 토큰
things like tokens and stuff.
같은 걸 검사할 수 있다면요
Um, but at any point you can always flip to using the Ulama API.
언제든 Ulama API 사용으로 전환할 수 있어요
If you would like to reduce API costs.
API 비용을 줄이고 싶다면요
So with that, that would be a wrap for a very substantive week, one with a lot of ground covered.
이로써 아주 중요한 한 주 작업이 끝났고 많은 걸 다뤄야 했죠
Next week we will be getting into using APIs for all of the frontier models.
다음 주에는 모든 프론티어 모델에 API를 사용할 거예요
So we'll be using OpenAI and Anthropic and Gemini.
오픈라이, 앤스로픽 제미니를 쓸 거예요
You'll do some work a little bit more.
비트 좀 더 줘요
Another step in the direction of agent ization of agentic AI with a little bit more work on agents.
에이전트 인공지능의 에이전트 아이즈로 가는 스텝으로 에이전트에 좀 더 집중했죠. 비트
But most importantly, we're going to be building some data science UIs using the fabulous Gradio platform
하지만 가장 중요한 건 데이터 과학 UI를 구축하는 겁니다 제가 좋아하는 그래디오 플랫폼을
that I love.
이용해서요
And we'll be doing that, including building a complete multimodal customer support agent that is able
그걸 할 겁니다 그림을 보여주거나 오디오를 만들 수 있는 완벽한 멀티모달 고객
to do things like show pictures and make audio and use tools where it calls into your computer.
지원 에이전트를 구축하는 것도요 여러분 컴퓨터로 호출되는 툴을 사용하는 거죠
So a lot to cover next week.
다음 주에 다룰 게 많아요
It's going to be a super exciting week and I can't wait to see you there.
정말 신나는 한 주가 될 거예요 빨리 보고 싶네요